hey guys this is going to be a video
that shows you my new latest glute
burnout I don't even have a name for it
I'm just calling it glute burnout in the
past I've had Brett's booty Blaster but
I like this more now so I'm I've been on
this constant quest to find the best
ways to burn out the glutes and this is
my current favorite so I have got
Camille here she has a mini band around
her knees and she's really strong she's
got two bands they're on her hips she's
got a strong band and an average band so
what she's going to do
here she starts out just with 20
abductions so this
targets the glutes there's not much else
firing other than the glutes and hip
external rotators so it's a way to kind
of pref fatigue them before she goes
into the hip thrust so here the glutes
are firing to produce hip abduction
torque and then she goes right into the
double band hip thrust and here here her
glutes are doing double duty because
they're firing the glutes are firing as
hip extensors and also as hip
abductors so this is really hard most of
my clients just use one band not the
purple band they don't throw the purple
one on top of the blue but Camille
strong she's done barbell hip thrust
with three 35 for two and now she takes
a narrow stance the reason why she takes
a narrow stance see see her glutes are
already on fire but if you get the
narrow stance now that band around her
knees is kind of inactive and you don't
need the hip abduction torque now it's
just mostly hip extension torque so you
full she's getting full hip extension
you can see at the top her torso is
level she gets some posterior tilt
action there and there that is 20 202 of
all three of them Camille you burning
yes very much so I've had six clients I
believe do these
uh Camille Diana Gabby
CG uh Carrie so there's five girls five
girls I've had do this and all five of
them have said it's the worst their
glutes have ever burned so give this a
try um if you don't have obviously most
of you won't have hip thrusters so you
can kind of set them up like in a power
rack you can use like a bench and put
the bands around a power Rack or you can
anchor the bands down with dumbbells um
but anyway give it a try see what you
think I think you're going to love it
thanks for watching